#war hold on hold on hold on no PA it's
not a real war it's not an actual War
it's not an actual War it's a Word War
it's not throw these terms around Chris
I
know first game of the NBA Finals was
tonight with the Miami Heat facing the
San Antonio Spurs Spurs are full of
geriatric players like Tim Duncan so in
honor of the Spurs tonight's hashtag is
elderly NBA examples would be Lamar
Oldman or minut this bowl of soup is
cold or H I've Chris pollen and I can't
get
up all right I want to put 60 seconds on
the clock and go Paul of Tomkins the Los
Angeles Clippers of coupons for cat food
which they're secretly
eating boys FR Gman Carl Malone because
All My Friends Are
Dead
yeah points b f again the Philadelphia
76ers works yeah points Heather Phoenix
Sons never visit me anymore
points Scotty I was in the first
production of
Pippen oh that's
hard points PA Tomkins just put my teeth
in a cup nothing but net
points Heather Campbell the Indiana paac
makers yes it's good points yeah course
BR
Elman Kevin Cosner sure to get an Oscar
Robinson for his wonderful performance
in Dancing With The
Wolves oh my
God I going to give you points but I
hope you left a breadcrumb trail as long
it took to get to the end
of